Tsuda, what's this I hear
about you buying a sex robot?
Boss, I—
Miss Tsuda, tell me you're not that kind of criminal.
Wait, no—
It's okay, Master.
We can be together forever and ever.
No!
Just a dream.
Look how cozily she's sleeping.
Wait, but robots don't sleep.
Is she broken?!
Maybe she's out of battery?
She has been turned on since she got here.
Okay, that should do it.
Wait, where's her power button?
Hmm. Maybe on her back?
Nope.
On the front?
Just a mole.
Oh my god, I'm being a total pervert right now!
But I can't leave her like this.
What's this?
A QR code!
Maybe I can learn something.
Thank you for your purchase.
This video will guide you through
the basics of your Nadeshiko sex android.
Let's start with booting her up.
Do I even need to turn her back on?
I don't want to get rid of her,
but maybe I should leave her off.
Ah, right, I forgot I ordered this.
Okay.
To activate the unit, give her a French kiss.
Then gently flip the switch inside her mouth.
Where is it? Where's the switch?
Master?
You're awake!
You wouldn't wake up,
so I was worried you were broken.
What a relief.
I completely forgot about charging my battery.
It's fine. I should've thought of it too.
But first, come here.
Um, Master? What is this?
All I had that fit you was my
school uniform, so I bought you this.
Although it has more
of a cosplay vibe than I expected.
It looks great on you.
You're adorable, Nadeshiko.
Did you just say my name?!
You did! You've never done that before!
I'm so happy.
Please keep calling me by my name.
Oh. Oh no.
She's so cute.
From now on, I'll enter sleep mode
when you do, Master.
S-Sure.
You can wake me up
in the same way you rebooted me.
Huh?
The same way as rebooting?!
It is a functional limitation of master registration.
REGISTERED
If you were registered,
all you would have to do is say my name.
NADESHIKO!
So you can either register as my master,
or manually wake me up every morning.
Which would you prefer?
Neither!